philosophy.com 2016-05-10

# privacy policy | philosophy

when you provide us with information through philosophy.com, we respect your privacy. it is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. we have a strict policy where we do not rent or sell your information to anyone, for any reason. if you have questions and/or concerns regarding the use of your data, our customer service department can be reached at 1-800-568-3151.

your visit to philosophy.com is subject to this privacy policy and our terms of use. please note that this privacy policy governs only information provided to philosophy.com and communications from philosophy.com. it does not govern any other information or communications that may reference philosophy, e.g., communications from other e-retailers or brick and mortar stores. this privacy policy was last updated 2016.

collection of personal information

we do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us or to one of our partners or affiliates. for example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or online survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group, gender, and product and/or cosmetic concerns, and the brands and products you use. if you decide to place an order, we will also need to know your delivery and billing address, credit card number and expiration date. to protect your personal information, users registering at philosophy.com must also enter a user name/email address and password. if you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us or our partners with any such information.

when you submit your personally identifiable information on philosophy.com, you are giving your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this privacy policy.

opt-in communications & third party involvement

if you make a purchase on philosophy.com or opt-in during the registration process or at other times when you submit personally identifiable information, the information you provide may be used by third-party marketing companies to assist us in hosting and storing your data who may from time to time assist in the maintenance and analysis of that data, and you may receive communications from philosophy.com or such third-party companies.

except as otherwise stated herein, we will never provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent. if you make a purchase on philosophy.com or specifically opt-in and later decide that you would no longer like to receive these communications, see the section “choice/opt out” below.

we may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions consistent with our privacy policy on our behalf. examples include customer support specialists, webhosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings), data analysis firms, and email service providers. such third parties may collect on our behalf or be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. your information may be transfered to servers that may be located in other countries, or to third parties based in other countries, so that they may process such information on our behalf. we carefully select our partners by ensuring that they adhere to strict privacy guidelines and will never sell or rent your information. if you prefer not to receive such opt-in communications, please do not opt-in to receive these communications.

if you elect to participate in any promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires, or other events during your visit to philosophy.com, your personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties pursuant to the rules or terms and conditions for those events with your explicit permission.

choice / opt-out

you may opt-out of receiving future opt-in communications from philosophy.com when you make a purchase on philosophy.com, register or otherwise provide your contact information to our customer service department. you may change your preferences at any time by revising your profile by unchecking the boxes for opt-in communications. you may also click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email opt-in communication you receive from us and follow the instructions provided therein.

use of collected information

if you have elected to provide us with your contact information, e.g., by registering on philosophy.com, emailing our customer service department, or placing an order, we may provide you with service related announcements concerning philosophy.com or contact you regarding your customer service requests or your order. for example, all registered users will receive a welcome email to confirm their registration. these types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns, and to provide the high level of customer service that philosophy.com offers its customers.

we may use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. we may collect, store, or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of philosophy.com, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. we may share or transfer non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees, and partners.

compliance with laws

we may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request. we may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

use of cookies & log files

we may place a “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user and personalize your experience. a cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track and target your preferences. the cookie will be stored on your computer’s hard drive until you remove it. we may also use temporary or “session” cookies to help you shop. these cookies will expire when you place an order. you can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. if you reject our cookies, you may still use philosophy.com, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features.

third party links

philosophy.com may contain links to or from other websites. please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. this privacy policy applies only to the information we collect on philosophy.com. we encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from philosophy.com or otherwise visit.

facebook

if you click "like" or make a comment on philosophy.com using a facebook social plugin, your activity may be published on facebook and shown to your facebook friends who visit philosophy.com. we encourage you to read the [facebook privacy policy](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php "facebook privacy policy") for more information.

notification of changes

we may revise this privacy policy from time to time. if we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the revised policy here. as we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this privacy policy. please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used. should there be any changes that would affect your opt-in status and how we use personal information, we will notify you to obtain permission.

updating your information

you have the ability to review, change and/or correct the personally identifiable information you provide us by calling 1-800-568-3151. if you are a registered user, you can also review, change or correct your personal information at any time by logging in to your account by clicking the log-in link on philosophy.com. you may request that we deactivate your account by calling us at 1-800-568-3151.

let us know how we are doing

we have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to philosophy.com is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by phone at 1-800-568-3151.

security

we implement various security measures in accordance with industry standards to protect the security of your personal information both online and offline. if you have any questions about security on philosophy.com, you can contact us at 1-800-568-3151.

\----------------------------------- 

LIVE JOYOUSLY OFFER   
terms and conditions 

To participate in this Offer, you must agree to and abide by these Terms & Conditions and the decisions of Sponsor/Administrator which are final and binding in all respects.

NO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER. INTERNET ACCESS AND VALID E-MAIL ACCOUNT IS REQUIRED.

Sponsor:

philosophy inc. (“Sponsor”), 350 5th Avenue, New York, NY 10118.

Eligibility:

The philosophy “live joyously Offer” (“Offer") is open to legal residents of the fifty (50) United States and District of Columbia, who are at least eighteen (18) years of age (or the age of majority in the jurisdiction of their residence, whichever is older) and who have Internet access and valid e-mail account. Void in Puerto Rico and where prohibited by law.

How to Participate:

The Offer ends May 15, 2015 at 11:59 p.m. ET, or when supplies are exhausted (whichever occurs first) (“Offer Period”). Sponsor’s computer is the official clock for this Offer.   
Follow the instructions on the Website to complete the entry form to receive one (1) Philosophy live joyously fragrance sample on card (15g of fragrance; $.01 value)(“Sample”). You will receive your sample in 2-4 weeks via USPS First-Class Mail®. 

LIMIT ONE (1) SAMPLE PER HOUSEHOLD DURING THE OFFER PERIOD.

SAMPLES ARE AVAILABLE ONLY WHILE SUPPLIES LAST. IF SUPPLIES OF SAMPLES ARE EXHAUSTED, SPONSOR AND ADMINISTRATOR SHALL NOT HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR THE OFFER. 

You may be asked to consent to receive promotional e-mails and reminder e-mails from Sponsor. Consenting to receive promotional or reminder e-mails is optional and does not have to be agreed upon in order to be eligible to participate in the Offer. In the event you do consent to receive these e-mails, the use of such e-mails shall be subject to the privacy policy of Sponsor and you may opt out of receiving these e-mails at any time. For Sponsor’s complete privacy policy, direct your Internet browser to <http://www.philosophy.com/terms/privacy-policy,en_US,pg.html>

Additional Restrictions:   
If using a mobile device to participate in the Offer, text and data rates/wireless Internet access charges may apply.

And, in such event, you will be charged by your wireless carrier in conjunction with participation in the Offer. Not all mobile devices offer wireless Internet access and can be used for participation in the Offer nor is wireless Internet access available in all areas.

Any and all costs involved in participating in the Offer are the sole responsibility of the participant. 

Sponsor and Administrator disclaim any and all liability for technological error, failure or malfunction of any kind in conjunction with participation in the Offer. Sponsor and Administrator are not responsible for late, lost, corrupted/garbled, misdirected, inaccessible/blocked, incomplete entry forms, all of which are void and will not result in receipt of a Sample; Sponsor and Administrator are also not responsible for “entry forms” which are submitted but do not result in the participant receiving a Sample due to technological error/failure/malfunction of any kind. Sponsor reserves the right to terminate, modify or suspend the Offer as it sees fit in its sole discretion without liability of any kind; in such event, Samples distributed prior to termination/modification/suspension of the Offer by Sponsor will be honored in accordance with their terms of use. Notice of such termination/modification/suspension will be posted on the Website. 

Any attempt to obtain a Sample other than in accordance with these Terms & Conditions or attempted participation in the Offer in a manner that seeks to undermine the integrity of the Offer (as determined by Sponsor/Administrator in their sole discretion) may constitute fraud and will result in withholding of Sample and disqualification from the Offer and future philosophy inc. promotions/offers. In such cases, Sponsor and Administrator reserve the right to pursue all available legal remedies so as to protect their respective interests. 

By participating in the Offer, you agree to release, indemnify and hold harmless Sponsor, Administrator, their respective parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, officers, directors, employees, agents, shareholders and representatives as well as Facebook, Inc. from any and all liability in conjunction with the Offer, including libel, slander, defamation, invasion of privacy or publicity, or other violation of third party rights, as well as for damage to your or a third party’s computer/mobile device (or information stored thereon). 

Sponsor’s failure to enforce any provision of these Terms & Conditions shall not function as the waiver of such provision.
